Fletcher Forum of World Affairs UP149
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1976 -- 2019; UP149.001; 1.75 Linear Feet; 1060 Digital Object(s)
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1991; UP149.001.00029
    - Book Review, 1991; UP149.001.00029.00015; Wunsch, James S.; Olowu, Dele; Goodland, Robert; Kornai, Jinos; de Zayas, Alfred-Maurice; Denitch, Bogdan; Lakoff, Sanford; York, Herbert F.; Shafir, Gershon; Holston, James; Glass, Charles; Nye Jr., Joseph S.; Binyan, Liu; Goldblatt, Howard; Hein, Lau
      Winter. The Failure of the Centralized State: Institutions and Self-Governance in Africa. Race to Save the Tropics: Ecology and Economics for a Sustainable Future. The Road to a Free Economy: Shifting from a Socialist System, The Case of Hungary. The Wehrmacht War Crimes Bureau, 1939-1945. The End of the Cold War. European Unity, Socialism and the Shift in Global Power. A Shield in Space? Technology, Politics, and the Strategic Defense Initiative. Land, Labor, and the Origins of the Israeli-Palestinian Conflict, 1882-1914. The Modernist City: An Anthropological Critique of Brasilia. Tribes With Flags: A Dangerous Passage through the Chaos of the Middle East. Bound to Lead: The Changing Nature of American Power. China's Crisis, China's Hope. Fueling Growth: The Energy Revolution and Economic Policy in Postwar Japan. Nicaragua's Other Revolution: Religious Faith and Political Struggle. Revolutions: Reflections on American Equality and Foreign Liberations.
    - Books received, 1991; UP149.001.00029.00016
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1991; UP149.001.00030 (Box 1)
    15, 2
    - Table of Contents, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00001
    - Forward, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00002
    - The "End" of the Cold War, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00003; Quester, George H.
    - Democracy and World Order, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00004; Roberts, Brad
    - Security in a Post-Hegemonic World, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00005; Nelson, Daniel N.
    - Toward A Mosaic Economy: Economic Relations in the Post-Cold War Era, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00006; Cohen, Benjamin J.
    - Human Rights in a Post-Cold War World, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00007; Forsythe, David P.
    - International Organization in the New World Order, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00008; Gordenker, Leon
    - The Foreign Policy of a United Germany, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00009
    - The Gulf War and the Environment, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00010; Toukan, Abdullah T
    - Perestroika and Human Rights: Steps in the Right Direction, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00011; Copeland, Emily A.
    - The Prospects for Democracy in the Southern Cone, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00012; Stephenson-Glade, Skye
    - A Regime for Trade in Services, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00013; Dow, Mark E.
    - Book Review, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00014; Habermas, Jiirgen; Weber Nicholsen, Shierry; Nye Jr., Joseph S.; Lasch, Christopher
      Summer. The New Conservatism: Cultural Criticism and the Historians' Debate. Bound to Lead: The Changing Nature of American Power. The True and Only Heaven: Progress and its Critics.
    - Book Review, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00015; Hill, Ronald J.; Zielonka, Jan; Hannum, Hurst; Payne, Richard J.; Inglehart, Robert; Sonn, Tamara; Lakoff, Robin Tolmach; Rock, Stephen R.; Handl, Giinther; Lutz, Robert E.; Schulzinger, Robert D.; Moreno, Dario; Heer, Nicholas; Duncan, W. Raymond; Ekedahl, Carolyn McGiffert; Rachwald, Arthur R.; Malan, Rian; Habermas, Jiirgen; Weber Nicholsen, Shierry; Nye Jr., Joseph S.; Woods, Randall Bennett; North, Robert C.
      Summer. Restructuring Eastern Europe: Towards a New European Order. Autonomy, Sovereignty, and Self-Determination: The Accommodation of Conflicting Rights. The Non-superpowers and South Africa: Implications for U.S. Policy. Culture Shift in Advanced Industrial Society. Between Qur'an and Crown: The Challenge of Political Legitimacy in the Arab World. Talking Power: The Politics of Language. Why Peace Breaks Out: Power Rapprochement in Historical Perspective. Transferring Hazardous Technologies and Substances: The International Legal Challenge. Henry Kissinger: Doctor of Diplomacy. US Policy in Central America: The Endless Debate. Islamic Law and Jurisprudence. Moscow and the Third World under Gorbachev. In Search of Poland: The Superpowers' Response to Solidarity, 1980-1989. My Traitor's Heart: A South African Exile Returns to Face His Country, His Tribe, and His Conscience. A Changing of the Guard: Anglo-American Relations, 1941-1946. War, Peace, Survival: Global Politics and Conceptual Synthesis.
    - Books received, 1991; UP149.001.00030.00016
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1992; UP149.001.00031 (Box 1)
    16, 1
    - Title Page, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00001
    - Table of Contents, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00002
    - Forward, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00003
    - Latin America's Trade Issues and Perspectives: A Skeptical View, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00004; Gongalves, Reinaldo
    - Selectivity and the Changing Structure of Trade Policy, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00005; Jones, Kent
    - Textiles and Apparel Trade in the 1990s: A Perspective from Jamaica, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00006; King, Ambassador Peter C.V.
    - The Political Economy of Service Sector Negotiations in the Uruguay Round, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00007; Aggarwal, Vinod K.
    - Environment and the Trading System, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00008; Adcock,J. Patrick; Kildow, Judith T.
    - How Can the Vision of a "New World Order" Be Realized?, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00009; Henrikson, Alan K.
    - Damage to Human Capital and the Economic Future of Burma, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00010; Maung, Mya
    - Single-Shot, Conditional Unilateral Arms Control Initiatives: Lessons from Six Cases, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00011; Rose, William M.
    - International Action on Climate Change and the Emergence of a Regime, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00012; Hoyt, Edward
    - Food and the Use of Force: The Role of Humanitarian Principles in the Gulf Crisis and Beyond, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00013; Shotwell, Major Charles B.
    - The Contested Country: Yugoslav Unity and Communist Revolution, 1919-1953, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00014; Djilas, Alexas; Book Review
    - Book Review, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00015; Borneman, John; Cairncross, Frances; Hilderbrand, Robert C.; Hourani, Albert; Tismaneau, Vladimir; Forsythe, David P.; Robinson, Linda; Brown, Janet Welsh; Seikaly, S.; Baalbaki, R.; Dodd, P.
      Winter. After the Wall: East Meets West in the New Berlin. Costing the Earth. Dumbarton Oaks: The Origins of the United Nations and the Search for Postwar Security. A History of the Arab Peoples. In Fairness to Future Generations: International Law, Common Patrimony, and Intergenerational Equity. In Search of Civil Society: Independent Peace Movements in the Soviet Bloc. The Internationalization of Human Rights. Intervention and Neglect: The United States and Central America Beyond the 1980s. In the U.S. Interest: Resources, Growth, and Security in the Developing World. Quest for Understanding: Arabic and Islamic Studies in Memory of Malcolm H. Kerr
    - Books received, 1992; UP149.001.00031.00016
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1992; UP149.001.00032
    16, 2
    - Table of Contents, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00001
    - Forward, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00002
    - Quebec's Urge: Autonomy or Independence?, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00003; Lisee, Jean-Francois; Bissonnette, Lise
    - Coping with the Nagorno-Karabakh Crisis, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00004; Goble, Paul A.
    - Testing the Moral Limits of Self-Determination: Northern Ireland and Croatia, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00005; Powers, Gerard F.
    - The Two Tiers of Ethnic Conflict in Western Europe, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00006; Messina, Anthony M.
    - Protracted Civil War in the Sudan: Its Future as a Multi-religious, Multi-ethnic State, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00007; Fluehr-Lobban, Carolyn
    - Pakistan: Islamic State, Ethnic Polity, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00008; Nasr, Seyyed Vali Reza
    - Peace Prospects for Yugoslavia, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00009; Pisiotis, Argyrios K.
    - South Africa's Transition to a Non-racial Democracy, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00010; Matisonn, John
    - Unity in Diversity: Reflections of a Born-Again European, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00011; Von Lazar, Arpad
    - New World Order and State Sovereignty: Implications for UN-Sponsored Intervention, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00012; Anderson, James H.
    - Driftnet Fishing in the North Pacific: Environmental and Foreign Policy Dimensions, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00013; Chang, Elaine
    - Sendero Luminoso: The Rise of a Revolutionary Movement, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00014; Harvey, Thomas
    - Italian Immigration: The Albanian Precedent, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00015; Salvi, Lucantino
    - The Changing Security Climate and the Future of NATO, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00016; Charles, Robert; Book Review
    - Book Review, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00017; Horwitz, Tony; Rosenberg, Tina; Lowenthal, Abraham F.; Dietrich, William S.; Chapman, William; Lincoln, Edward J.; Westbrook, Robert; Sick, Gary; Kellas, James G.; Hersh, Seymour; Buchanan, Allen; Auletta, Ken; Ruiz, Ramon Eduardo
      Summer.Bagdad Without a Map. Children of Cain: Violence and the Violent in Latin America. Exporting Democracy: The United States and Latin America. In the Shadow of the Rising Sun: The Political Roots of American Economic Decline. Inventing Japan: The Making of a Postwar Civilization. Japan's Unequal Trade. John Dewey and the American Democracy. October Surprise: America's Hostages in Iran and the Election of Ronald Reagan. The Politics of Nationalism and Ethnicity. The Samson Option. Secession: The Morality of Political Divorce from Fort Sumter to Quebec. Three Blind Mice: How the TV Networks Lost Their Way. Triumphs and Tragedy: A History of the Mexican People.
    - Books received, 1992; UP149.001.00032.00018
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1993; UP149.001.00033
    17, 1
    - Title Page, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00001
    - Table of Contents, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00002
    - Forward, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00003
    - A Free Society or a Free Press - Which Comes First?, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00004; Grunwald, Henry
    - The Triumph of Western News Communication, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00005; Hachten, William
    - Will Russia's Free Press Survive?, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00006; Daniloff, Nicholas
    - The Media in Emerging African Democracies: Power, Politics and the Role of the Press, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00007; Chinje, Eric
    - Television's Impact on Executive Decisionmaking and Diplomacy, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00008; McNulty, Timothy J.
    - Telecommunications and Regional Interdependence in Southeast Asia, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00009; Jussawalla, Meheroo
    - European Telecommunications Policy and Open Network Provision: The Evolution of a Regulatory Methodology, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00010; Austin, Mark T.
    - European Community Law and Broadcasting: The Dutch Case, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00011; Pelle, Josephina J.A.
    - The International Ozone Regime: Concessions and Loopholes, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00012; Vorlat, Katrien
    - The Nature of Saudi Arabian Strategic Power: Implications for American Foreign Policy, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00013; Mirkow, Frank J.
    - Curbing Rapid Population Growth: The Crux of Sustainable Development, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00014; Wendel, Christopher S.
    - A Study of Peaceful Revolution: The Philippines, 1986, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00015; Sawin, Janet L.
    - Book Review, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00016; MacDonald, Douglas J.; Rosen, George; Cohen, Robin; Goulbourne, Harry; Ehteshami, Anoushirvan; Varasteh, Manshour; Francks, Penelope; Piel, Gerard; Jennings, Sir Robert Y.; Watts, Sir Arthur; Brown, Cheryl J.; Schraub, Timber M.; Palmer, David Scott; Sapolsky, Harvey; Crane, Rhonda; Neuman, W. Russell; Noam, Eli M.
      Winter. Adventures in Chaos: American Intervention for Reform in the Third World. Contrasting Styles of Industrial Reform: China and India in the 1980s. Democracy and Socialism in Africa. Iran and the International Community. Japanese Economic Development: Theory and Practice. Only One World: Our Own to Make and Keep. Oppenheim's International Law, Ninth Edition, Volume I, Peace. Resolving Third World Conflict: Challenges for a New Era. Shining Path of Peru. The Telecommunications Revolution: Past, Present and Future.
    - Books received, 1993; UP149.001.00033.00017
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1993; UP149.001.00034
    17, 2
    - Table of Contents, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00001
    - Forward, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00002
    - The Politics of Identity in International Relations, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00003; Peterson, V Spike
    - Feminist Standpoint Theory Meets International Relations Theory: A Feminist Version of David and Goliath?, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00004; Zalewski, Marysia
    - Gender and International Human Rights, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00005; Deutz, Andrew M.
    - Third World Women in the Global Factory: Neither "Victims" nor "Saviors", 1993; UP149.001.00034.00006; Runyan, Inne Sisson
    - Gender and Middle East Politics, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00007; Sharoni, Simona
    - National Selves and Feminine Others, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00008; True, Jacqui
    - Gendered Nationalism and "New" Nation-States: "Democratic Progress" in Eastern Europe, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00009; Mayhall, Stacey L.
    - Development and Women's Political Leadership: The Missing Link in Sub-Saharan Africa, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00010; Foster, Annie
    - The Twilight of Sovereignty, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00011; Wriston, Walter B.
    - Philippine Foreign Policy: New Policy in a Changing World Environment, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00012; Romulo, Roberto R.
    - Bonehead Non-Proliferation, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00013; Koplow, David A.
    - The Hour of Europe: Lessons from the Yugoslav Conflict, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00014; Guicherd, Catherine
    - Beyond Collective Security: The Case for a Democratic Security System in Europe, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00015; Karl, David J.
    - International Law and Non-Intervention: When Do Humanitarian Concerns Supersede Sovereignty?, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00016; Arnison, Nancy D.
    - Book Review, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00017; Finnegan, William; Kennan, George; Giannou, Chris; Hewett, Ed A.; Gaddy, Clifford; Yousaf, Mohammad; Adkin, Mark; Deng, Francis; Minear, Larry; Wriston, Walter B.; Thompson, Edward T.
      Summer. A Complicated War: The Harrowing of Mozambique. Around the Cragged Hill: A Personal and Political Philosophy. Besieged: A Doctor's Story of Life and Death in Beirut. Open for Business: Russia's Return to the Global Economy. The Bear Trap: Afghanistan's Untold Story. The Challenges of Famine Relief. Emergency Operations in the Sudan. The Twilight of Sovereignty. Theodore H. White at Large: The Best of His Magazine Writing, 1939-1986.
    - Books received, 1993; UP149.001.00034.00018
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1994; UP149.001.00035 (Box 1)
    Winter/Spring
    18, 1
    - Title Page, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00001
    - Table of Contents, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00002
    - In the Absence of War: Employing America's Military Capabilities in the 1990s, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00003; Miller, Admiral Paul David
    - Will the United States Lead a New World Order?, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00004; Howe, Admiral Jonathan T. (Ret.)
    - Non-Traditional Missions and the Future of the U.S. Military, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00005; Rosenau, William
    - Creating a U.N. Peace Enforcement Force: A Case for U.S. Leadership, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00006; Harper, Captain Gregory P.
    - The Fiction of a U.N. Standing Army, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00007; Morrison, Alex
    - A Twenty-First Century Vision for Economic Assistance, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00008; Anderson, G. William
    - Understanding the U.N. Conventional Arms Register, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00009; Taylor, Colonel Terence T.
    - Dispute Settlement Provisions in the NAFTA and the CAFTA: Progress or Protectionism?, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00010; Moody-O'Grady, Kristin A.
    - The Role of the CIA in Economic and Technological Intelligence, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00011; Foley, Timothy D.
    - Review Essay, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00012; Kohli, Atul; Rudolph, Lloyd; Rudolph, Susanne H.; Vanaik, Achin; Book Review
      Winter/Spring. India's Democracy: An Analysis of Changing State-Society Relations. Democracy and Discontent: India's Growing Crisis of Governability. In Pursuit of Lakshmi: The Political Economy of the Indian State. The Painful Transition: Bourgeois Democracy in India.
    - Book Review, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00013; Ottaway, Marina; Horvdth, Agnes; Szakolczai, Arpad; Lynn-Jones, Sean M.; Miller, Steven; Kotkin, Joel; Nathan, James A.; Peters, John E.
      Winter/Spring. South Africa: The Struggle for a New World Order. The Dissolution of Communist Power: The Case of Hungary. The Cold War and After: Prospects for Peace, Expanded Edition. Tribes: How Race, Religion and Identity Determine Success in the New Global Economy. The Cuban Missile Crisis Revisited. The U.S. Military: Ready for the New World Order?.
    - Books received, 1994; UP149.001.00035.00014
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1994; UP149.001.00036 (Box 1)
    Summer/Fall
    18, 2
    - Table of Contents, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00001
    - An Interview with Telford Taylor, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00002; Maguire, Linda
    - The War Crimes Tribunal for the Former Yugoslavia: Problems and Prospects, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00003; Laber, Jeri; Nizich, Ivana
    - Forgetting "The Policies and Practices of the Past": Impunity in Cambodia, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00004; Marks, Stephen P.
    - War Crimes: The Case of Iraq, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00005; Robbins, James S.
    - U.S. Tort Suits by Aliens Based on International Law, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00006; Rubin, Alfred P.
    - Obstacles to the Creation of a Permanent War Crimes Tribunal, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00007; Blakesley, Christopher L.
    - Is a Permanent Nuremberg on the Horizon?, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00008; Drinan, S.j., Robert F
    - American Television and Cinema in France and Europe, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00009; Quintero, Diana
    - Heavenly Junk, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00010; Finch, Jr., Ambassador Edward R.
    - Restructuring the United States' Export Control Legislation for the Post-Cold War Era, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00011; Alam, Shahid
    - Kennan at 90: Still in Search of Mr. X, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00012; Grann, David
    - The Gulf Crisis: An Attempt to Understand, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00013; Algosaibi, Ghazi A.; Barzilai, Gad; Klieman, Aharon; Shidlo, Gil; Freedman, Robert O.; Book Review
      Summer/Fall. The Gulf Crisis: An Attempt to Understand. The Gulf Crisis and Its Global Aftermath. The Middle East After Iraq's Invasion of Kuwait.
    - Book Review, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00014; Irwin, Steven M.; Branscomb, Lewis; Keller, Maryann; McFaul, Michael; Markov, Sergei; Fisher, Lois; Tourevski, Mark; Morgan, Eileen; Munch, Richard; Smelser, Neil J.; Blair, Bruce G.; Hurrel, Andrew; Kingsbury, Benedict; Zaprudnik, Jan
      Summer/Fall. Technology Policy and America's Future. Empowering Technology: Implementing a U.S. Strategy. Collision: GM, Toyota, Volkswagen and the Race to Own the 21st Century. The Troubled Birth of Russian Democracy: Parties, Personalities, and Programs. Survival in Russia: Chaos and Hope in Everyday Life. Cutting the Red Tape: How Western Companies Can Profit in the New Russia. Theory of Culture. The Logic of Accidental Nuclear War. The International Politics of the Environment: Actors, Interests, and Institutions. Belarus: At a Crossroads in History.
    - Books received, 1994; UP149.001.00036.00015
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1995; UP149.001.00037
    19, 1
    - Title Page, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00001
    - Table of Contents, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00002
    - A "Nutshell" Approach to the U.N. Human Rights Law Protecting Minorities, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00003; Newman, Frank C.
    - States, Nations, and Resources: An Interdependent Relationship?, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00004; Clay, Jason W.
    - Safeguards for Minorities Versus Sovereignty of Nations, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00005; Bose, Sugata
    - South Africa: Minority Conflict and the Legacy of Minority Rule, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00006; Manby, Bronwen
    - National Minorities: A Global, European, and Swiss Perspective, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00007; Thurer, Daniel G.
    - Chiapas: The First Post-Modem Revolution, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00008; Carrigan, Ana
    - An Interview with Lani Guinier, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00009
    - Public Perceptions of U.N. Peacekeeping, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00010; Lehmann, Ingrid A.
    - Technology and Advances in Foreign Military Capabilities, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00011; Peters, John E.
    - Integrating the U.S. Industrial Base, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00012; Foster, Gregory D.
    - The $10 Billion Question: AIPAC and Loan Guarantees to Israel, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00013; Foster, Gregory D.
    - Review Essay, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00014; Gerson, Allan; Book Review
      Winter/Spring. The Kirkpatrick Mission: Diplomacy Without Apology: America at the United Nations 1981-1985.
    - Book Review, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00015; Ackerman, Peter; Kruegler, Christopher; Aspe, Pedro; Naim, Moises; Moore, Lieutenant General Harold G. USA (retired); Galloway, Joseph L.; Fallows, James; Susskind, Lawrence E.
      Winter/Spring. Strategic Non-Violent Conflict: The Dynamics of People Power in the Twentieth Century. Economic Transformation the Mexican Way. Paper Tigers and Minotaurs: The Politics of Venezuela's Economic Reforms. We Were Soldiers Once... and Young. Looking At the Sun: The Rise of the New East Asian Economic and Political System. Environmental Diplomacy: Negotiating More Effective Global Agreements.
    - Books received, 1995; UP149.001.00037.00016
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1995; UP149.001.00038
    19, 2
    - Table of Contents, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00001
    - Constructive Containment, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00002; Henrikson, Alan K.
    - The Moral and Legal Basis for Sanctions, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00003; D'Amato, Anthony
    - Beyond Neutrality: On the Compatibility of Military Intervention and Humanitarian Assistance, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00004; Donini, Antonio
    - Diplomacy and Human Rights: The Role of Human Rights in Conflict Resolution in El Salvador and Haiti, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00005; Bar-Yaacov, Nomi
    - The Sanctions Era: An Alternative to Military Intervention, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00006; Lopez, George; Cortright, David
    - American Power and American Diplomacy, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00007; Lake, Anthony
    - The Carter Mission to Haiti: Unintended Consequences for Human Rights Law, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00008; Williams, Jeffrey A.; Petrie, John N.
    - Structural Adjustment Programs in Sub-Saharan Africa, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00009; O'Brien, David P.
    - Truman's Bomb, Our Bomb, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00010; Frank, Casey
    - From Silk to Satellite: A Letter from Central Asia, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00011; Tehranian, Majid
    - Book Review, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00012; Bahpai, Kanti P.; Cohen, Stephen P; Hancock, M. Donald; Welsh, Helga A.; Mesbahi, Mohiaddin; Bailey, Kathleen C.; Goertemaker, Manfred; Pearson, Frederic S.
      Summer/Fall. Review Essay: South Asia After the Cold War: International Perspectives. German Unification: Process and Outcome. Central Asia and the Caucasus after the Soviet Union: Domestic and International Dynamics. Strengthening Nuclear Non-Proliferation. Unifying Germany, 1989-1990. The Global Spread of Arms: Political Economy of International Security.
    - Books received, 1995; UP149.001.00038.00013
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 1996; UP149.001.00039 (Box 1)
    20, 1